Guide to the Brooklyn location scouting photographs collection CBHM.0017
Center for Brooklyn History
- Series 25: Fort Greene, circa 1990 - 2011
  - Fort Greene Monument [The Prison Ship Martyrs' Monument], circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Masonic Temple, 312 Clermont Avenue, circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - INT Auditorium, Brooklyn Masonic Temple, 317 Clermont Avenue, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 271 Clermont Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Lafayette Avenue), Fort Greene, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 258 Carlton Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue), Fort Greene, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 73 Willoughby Avenue (between Clermont Avenue and Vanderbilt Avenue), 2005 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 175 Lafayette Avenue (between Adelphi Street and Clermont Avenue), 2005 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 348 Adelphi Street (between Lafayette Avenue and Greene Avenue), 2005 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 251 Clermont Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue), Fort Greene, 2005 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 257 Carlton Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Willoughby Avenue), Fort Greene, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - EXT Backyard, Brooklyn Brownstone, 281 Clermont Avenue (between Dekalb Avenue and Lafayette Avenue), Fort Greene, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - INT Bathroom, Brooklyn Masonic Temple, 317 Clermont Avenue at Lafayette Avenue, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - EXT Streets, Park Avenue (between Carlton Avenue and Vanderbilt Avenue), 2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - EXT Church, French Speaking Baptist Church, 209 Clermont Avenue at Willoughby Avenue, 2007 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - French Speaking Baptist Church, 209 Clermont Avenue (at Willoughby Avenue), 2007 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - INT Training room, Masonic Temple, 317 Clermont Avenue at Lafayette Avenue, 2008 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 375 Carlton Avenue, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 289 Cumberland Street, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black Residence, 214 Cumberland Street, Fort Greene, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 254 Adelphi Street, Fort Greene, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse - Abby Black, 259 Clermont Avenue at Dekalb Avenue, Fort Greene, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - INT/EXT various Blacks, 120 South Elliott Place, Fort Greene, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT Black residence, 321 Adelphi Street, Fort Greene, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT Black residence, 258 Carlton Avenue, Fort Greene, 2010 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black, 185 Lafayette Avenue, 2010 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - INT/EXT Abby Black Residence, 287 Cumberland Street, Fort Greene, 2010 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 329 Adelphi Street at Lafayette Avenue, 2010 (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - EXT Subway station, Lafayette Avenue Station, Fort Greene, circa 2010 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - EXT Subway station, Lafayette Avenue Station 2, Fort Greene, circa 2010 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - INT TV Studio, BRIC Studios, BCAT [Brooklyn Cable Access TV], 57 Rockwell Place (between Fulton Street and Dekalb Avenue), Fort Greene, circa 2010 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Fort Greene Park, missing persons wall, circa 2010 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Various Black, 68 South Elliott Place, Fort Greene, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse, 204 Adelphi Street, between Willoughby Avenue and Dekalb Avenue, Fort Greene, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - INT/EXT Various Black, 130 South Oxford Street, Fort Greene, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Townhouse - Abby, 177 Adelphi Street, between Willoughby Avenue and Myrtle Avenue, Fort Greene, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - EXT Fort Greene, South Oxford Street at Dekalb Avenue, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Various Black, 11 South Oxford Street, Fort Greene, 2011 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Series 26: Gerritsen Beach, 2011
  This series includes only one folder.
  Series 26: Gerritsen Beach includes one folder of photographs of streets in the Gerritsen Beach neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Gerritsen Beach, 2011 (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Series 27: Gowanus, circa 1990 - 2010
  Series 27: Gowanus includes photographs of restaurants, bars, public housing, manufacturing and industrial areas, and streets in the Gowanus neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - Gowanus neighborhood, circa 1990 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Monte Venetian Room [Monte's Italian Restaurant], circa 1990 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Funeral parlor, Gomez Funeral Service, 162 4th Avenue at Douglass Street, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - EXT Club La Habanita, Lot at 232 4th Avenue between President Street and Union Street, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Industrial street, Smith Street at Huntington Street, Gowanus, circa 1995 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Neighborhood street, 3rd Avenue at Carroll Street, 4th Avenue at Carroll Street, Goawnus, circa 1995 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - EXT Neighborhood Bar, Hennessy's Old Ale House, 3rd Avenue at 10th Street, circa 1995 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Neighborhood street, 3rd Avenue at 11th Street, Gowanus, circa 1995 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - EXT Highway, Gowanus Expressway, circa 1995 (Box 85, Folder 1)
  - EXT Gun drop, 6th Street, Sanitation Department at end of 2nd Avenue, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Red Hook Crushers, Inc., 186 3rd Street, Gowanus Canal and 3rd Avenue, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Smith Street at 5th Street, 1995 (Box 48)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Gowanus, Smith Street and 9th Street, Luquer Street, Nelson Street, Huntington Street, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, Apartment #1, 121 3rd Street at Bond Street, Gowanus, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Carroll Street Bridge over Gowanus Canal, circa 2000 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Factory space / Club, Jewish Press, "The Void Room," 2nd Floor, 3rd Avenue between 1st Street and 3rd Street, circa 2000 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    This location was scouted for The Beat. This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Warehouses."
  - Hennessy's Old Ale House, 173 3rd Avenue at 10th Street, circa 2000 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - INT Hotel laundry, Rose Linen, 267 Douglass Street between Nevins Street and 3rd Avenue, 2002 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - 3rd Avenue under the Gowanus Expressway, 2003 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - INT Soul Brothers, Glory Social Club, 282 3rd Avenue (between Carroll Street and President Street), 2004 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Waterfront Disposal, 110 5th Street (off 2nd Avenue), Gowanus, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Gowanus Houses, Baltic Street and Bond Street, Gowanus, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - La Flor del Paraiso, 520 4th Avenue (at 12th Street), [Gowanus], 2004 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - 51 - 63 9th Street (off 9th Street Bridge), between Smith Street and 2nd Avenue, Gowanus, circa 2005 (Box 86, Folder 3)
  - EXT/INT School, P.S. 133, 4th Avenue (between Butler Street and Baltic Street), 2007 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - EXT Yard (leading to boat), 426 President Street at Bond Street, Gowanus, 2011 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Yards leading to Jerko [426 President Street, Gowanus], 2011 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Thomas Greene Playground, 3rd Avenue at Nevins Street, circa 2010 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - 6th Borough, Gowanus Canal, 2010 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Carroll Street Bridge, 388 - 400 Carroll Street (between Bond Street and Nevins Street), 2010 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Series 28: Gravesend, 1987-2011
  Series 28: Gravesend includes photographs of restaurants, bars, stores, public housing, churches, and streets in the the Gravesend neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - La Mer [Caterers], Ocean Parkway (Chateau Bleu), 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Neighborhood Bar: McDonald Avenue Hideout, 2341a McDonald Avenue, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - EXT Streets, Shore Parkway between 25th Avenue and Bay 41st Street, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - EXT Electronics store: Big Daddy, 435 Kings Highway, 2002 (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - EXT Stephen Crane Houses, Marlboro Houses, Building 2 - Rear Entrance, 30 Avenue V - Apartment 5E, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 3, Oversize 1)
    This location was scouted for American Gangster. This folder includes blueprints of the Marlboro Houses.
  - EXT Project Buildings [Marlboro Houses], 2006 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - EXT Project Grounds - Marlboro Houses, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - EXT Marlboro Houses, Building 3, 2250 East 11th Street, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - INT Marlboro Houses, Apartment 1G, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - INT Project Apartment, Marlboro Houses, 2295 West 11th Street, Apartment 1F, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - EXT Marlboro Houses, Survey Building 1, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - INT Apartment, Marlboro Houses, Building 3, 2250 East 11th Street Apartment 2G, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - INT Project Apartment, Marlboro Houses, 2250 West 11th Street, Apartment 3D, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - I/E Stephen Crane Houses, Marlboro Houses, Building 11, 2220 West 11th Street, First Floor Hallway, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - I/E Marlboro Houses, Halls and Roofs, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT Marlboro Houses, Hallways/Staircases/Front, 2006 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - South Street alternative: McDonald Avenue, Gravesend Neck Road, Village Road South, Avenue W, Avenue X, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - South Street alternative: Avenue X, Bouck Court, Avenue Y, Cobek Court, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - South Street alternative: Shell Road, Shore Parkway, West 6th Street, 2007 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - EXT Church, Trinity Tabernacle, 121 Gravesend Neck Road, circa 2007 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Stillwell Avenue between Avenue U and Avenue X, circa 2010 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Pier, "End of the World," Bay 43rd Street at Shore Parkway, 2011 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Series 29: Greenpoint, circa 1990 - circa 2010
  Series 29: Greenpoint includes photographs of restaurants, bars, manufacturing and industrial areas, apartments, schools, stores, churches, and streets in the Greenpoint neighborhood of Brooklyn.
  - EXT Car chase, truck crashes through fence and lot at Quay Street and Franklin Street, circa 1990 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - EXT Joe's Apartment: 73 Meserole Street at Guernsey Street, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Greenpoint [India Street Pier?], circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Greenpoint Little League field, Vandervoort Avenue and Division Place, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - EXT Chase, P/U crashes through fence, W. H. Christian and Sons parking lot, 31 Franklin Street at Quay Street, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - EXT Joe and Pearl walk and talk, Manhattan Avenue and Green Street, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT J and D's Inn, 579 Meeker Avenue (between North Henry Street and Monitor Street), Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - EXT Tavern, former tavern, Calyer Street at Franklin Street, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Bar, McGinn's Bar, 916 Manhattan Avenue at Greenpoint Avenue, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT North Greenpoint Concerned Citizens Club, Huron Street and Franklin Street, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - McGinn's Bar, Greenpoint Avenue and Manhattan Avenue, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Joe's roof moonshot, Russell Street, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    This location was scouted for Used People. This folder was categorized under "Brooklyn Rooftops and Theaters."
  - EXT joe's roof/moonshot, dusk shots, 57 Russell Street, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - EXT Joe and Pearl walk and talk, Norman Avenue and Manhattan Avenue, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Greenpoint Terminal, circa 1990 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - EXT Joe's apartment, 145 Engert Avenue, 153 Engert Avenue, circa 1990 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Bar, Park Place: 143 Driggs Avenue at Russell Street, Greenpoint, circa 1990 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Sutton Street, Driggs Avenue, Nassau Avenue, Diamond Street, Kingsland Avenue, 1991 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - 144 Franklin Street at Greenpoint Avenue, 3rd floor, 1992 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - EXT Joe and Pearl Walk and Talk, Manhattan Avenue and Eagle Street, Greenpoint, 1992 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - EXT Warehouse, Greenpoint Terminal, Noble Street and West Street, Greenpoint, 1993 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Storefront, 79 Greenpoint Avenue (between Franklin Street and Manhattan Avenue), circa 1995 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Pit Stop Bar, 152 Meserole at McGuiness Boulevard, Greenpoint, circa 1995 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Greenpoint Terminal, West Street and Noble Avenue, 5th Floor Main Building, circa 1995 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Meeker Street and Apollo Street, Meeker Street and Monitor Street, circa 1995 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Shop or stage space, Nulux Incorporated, 112 Green Street (between Franklin Street and Manhattan Avenue), Greenpoint, circa 1995 (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Commercial Street and Dupont Street, baseball field, Greenpoint [Newtown Barge Playground], circa 1995 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Gerke's of Greenpoint, 750 Manhattan Avenue, Greenpoint, circa 1995 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - INT/EXT Bar, Palace Cafe, 206 Nassau Avenue at Russell Street, circa 1995 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Irene's Bar, 156 Calyer Street at Lorimer Street, Greenpoint, 1995 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Greenpoint Travel, 783 Manhattan Avenue, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - EXT Truck yard: Truck Rite Corp, 360 Kingsland Avenue, 1995 (Box 50, Folder 24)
  - New York Docks / Warehouse, Greenpoint Terminal, Noble Street and West Street, 1995 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Gerke's of Greenpoint, 750 Manhattan Avenue, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - EXT Coffee Shop, 631 Manhattan Avenue, 6 Nassau Avenue, Greenpoint, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - EXT/INT Hallway/Johnny's apartment, 222 Kingsland Avenue between Driggs Avenue and Nassau Avenue, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - INT Bar: Polish National Home, 261 Driggs Avenue at Eckford Street, 1996 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - INT Sheriff's Apartment, 222 Richardson Street, 1st Floor (between Monitor Street and North Henry Street), Greenpoint, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - EXT Bridge, Pulaski Bridge, View from McGuinness Boulevard at Box Street, Brooklyn side, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - INT Empty Apartments, 34 Driggs Avenue at Sutton Street, Greenpoint, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Shabby Office, 909 Manhattan Avenue between Greenpoint Avenue and Kent Street, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Greenpoint, Oak Street and Kent Street, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Greenpoint, Meserole Avenue and Newel Street, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Greenpoint, Driggs Avenue and Leonard Street, 1997 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Shop Space, Box Street at base of McGuinness Boulevard bridge [Pulaski Bridge], Greenpoint, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - EXT Neighborhood, Greenpoint Park [Newtown Barge Playground], Franklin Street and Dupont Street, 1997 (Box 73, Folder 3)
  - INT restaurant, Palace Restaurant [Palace Café], 206 Nassau Avenue at Russell Street, 1998 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - INT apartment, 92 India Street between Manhattan Avenue and Franklin Street, Greenpoint, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    This folder was categorized under "Brookyln Apartments."
  - INT Apartment, 129 Java Street (between Manhattan Avenue and Franklin Street), Greenpoint, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - INT Kia's Apartment, 113 Kent Street between Franklin Street and Manhattan Avenue, Greenpoint, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - INT Kia's apartment, 115 1/2 India Street between Franklin Street and Manhattan Avenue, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - INT Apartment, 80 India Street (between Manhattan Avenue and Franklin Street), Greenpoint, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - INT Apartment, 114 Kent Street, Greenpoint, 1999 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - INT Apartment, 117 Kent Street between Franklin Street and Manhattan Avenue, 1999 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - Neighborhood Street, Messerole Avenue at Eckford Street, Greenpoint, circa 2000 (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - INT Pick-up Truck (Street near Warehouse), Wythe Avenue, Berry Street, North 11th Street, Kent Avenue, Greenpoint, Brooklyn, circa 2000 (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - India Street between McGuinness Boulevard and Provost Street, circa 2000 (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Greenpoint Scrap Metal, 304 Greenpoint Avenue at Moultrie Street, circa 2000 (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - INT/EXT Law Office: JP Clark Company, 127 Nassau Avenue, circa 2000 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - INT Shop Space, Old Vanguard Corporation Property, 10 Java Street at the river, Greenpoint, circa 2000 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Manhattan Avenue at Newtown Creek, circa 2000 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Greenpoint Terminal Market, circa 2000 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - EXT Bridge, Pulaski Bridge, circa 2000 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Franklin Street and Milton Street, circa 2000 (Box 86, Folder 8)
  - EXT Streets, Greenpoint Terminal, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    This folder includes photographs of Meeker Avenue at Skillman Avenue, Gardner Avenue under the Kosciuszko Bridge, Thomas Street and Gardner Avenue, and Greenpoint Avenue and West Street.
  - INT/EXT Bar: Irene's, 156 Calyer Street at Lorimer Street, Greenpoint, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 39)
  - Loft / Courtyard, Greenpoint Terminal Market, West Street and Noble Street, 2002 (Box 30, Folder 40)
  - 246 Kingsland Avenue between Nassau Avenue and Driggs Avenue, circa 2002 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - INT/EXT Artist's Loft, Brooklyn Stage and Studio, 259 Green Street at Provost Street, Greenpoint, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 41)
  - INT/EXT Greenpoint Terminal, West Street at Noble Street, Greenpoint, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 42)
  - McGolrick Park, Nassau Avenue at Monitor Street, Greenpoint, 2003 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Greenpoint neighborhood, 2003 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    This folder includes photographs of Milton Street, Kent Street, Franklin Street, Guernsey Street at Oak Street, and Manhattan Avenue at Milton Street.
  - CLS Warehouse, 10 Java Street, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - INT/EXT Storefront, 70 Greenpoint Avenue (between Franklin Street and West Street), Greenpoint, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - EXT Tripod Takedown, Greenpoint Terminal and Watertower, Noble Street and West Street, Greenpoint, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    This location was scouted for War of the Worlds and considered for American Gangster.
  - EXT Water's Edge, Meeker Avenue and Gardner Avenue, Greenpoint [Newtown Creek], 2004 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - INT/EXT Law Office, Lucas and Balis, 125 Nassau Avenue, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - GMDC [Greenpoint Manufacturing and Design Center], 1155 Manhattan Avenue at Ash Street, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - EXT Waterfront, Greenpoint Terminal Market, Noble Street at Kent Avenue, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - EXT Intersection, North Henry Street at Herbert Street, Greenpoint, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Alley, 85 Java Street and 182 Franklin Street, Greenpoint, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - El Naranjito, 162 Franklin Street between Java Street and Kent Street, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - EXT/INT Warehouse, Greenpoint, 271 Kent Street at Provost Street, 2004 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - INT/EXT Law Office: 945 Manhattan Avenue, 2004 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - 561 Manhattan Avenue, Apt. 3, corner of Driggs Avenue, 2004 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Rudy's Place, 180 Franklin Street, 2004 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - INT Apartment, 1139 Manhattan Avenue at Box Street, 2nd Floor, Apartment 2, Greenpoint, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Cherry Street, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Commercial Street and Clay Street, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Greenpoint, Clay Street at Commercial Street, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Warehouse, Oak Street, Greenpoint, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - INT St. Cecilia, 84 Herbert Street, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - INT High School Gym, St. Anthony / St. Alphonsus Church, 862 Manhattan Avenue, circa 2005 (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Greenpoint, Dupont Street and Clay Street, circa 2005 (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Brooklyn streets, circa 2005 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    This folder contains photographs of under Pulaski Bridge at McGuinness Boulevard and Ash Street, Provost Street and Freeman Street, Greenpoint Avenue and North Henry Street, and Greenpoint Avenue and Moultrie Street.
  - EXT Vacant Lot, Monuments Field Office Park, Greenpoint, West of West Street, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Galeria Kuriera Plus, 145 Java Street (between Manhattan Avenue and Franklin Street), Greenpoint, 2005 (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - EXT Tripod takedown, Greenpoint Terminal, 2005 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Lot / Vacant building, Garbage transfer, West Street (between Calyer Place and Quay Street), Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 22)
  - INT Loft / Art space, 70 Greenpoint Avenue, Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 23)
  - INT Storefront, 70 Commercial Street, Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 24)
  - EXT / INT Brooklyn Loft, 157 West Street between Huron Street and India Street, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 25)
  - EXT Street/Houses, Lorimer Street and Norman Avenue, Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 26)
  - EXT Street/Houses, Humboldt Street (between Nassau Avenue and Norman Avenue), Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - EXT/INT Loft, Broadway Stages, 203 Meserole Avenue (Office), 220 West Street (between Freeman Street and Eagle Street), 2006 (Box 31, Folder 28)
  - Broadway Stages, 259 Green Street (between McGuiness Boulevard and Provost Street), Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 29)
  - EXT/INT Brooklyn Loft, 259 Green Street at Provost Street (between McGuiness Boulevard and Provost Street), Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - EXT Street, Leonard Street between Driggs Avenue and Nassau Avenue, Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 9)
  - EXT Street, Eckford Street and Meserole Avenue, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 11)
  - Oak Street between Guernsey Street and Franklin Street, Greenpoint, 2006 (Box 86, Folder 12)
  - Bay Crane, circa 2007 (Box 31, Folder 30)
  - EXT Union Baptist Church, 153 Noble Street (between Lorimer Street and Manhattan Avenue), 2007 (Box 31, Folder 31)
  - EXT East River / Impound lot, Tri-State Lumber, 11 West Street between Quay Street and Calyer Place, 2008 (Box 31, Folder 32)
  - INT Auction room, The Warsaw at the Polish National Home, 261 Driggs Avenue between Eckford Street and Leonard Street, 2008 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment building, 221 Franklin Street, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment building, 1035 Manhattan Avenue, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment, 145 Noble Street, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment, 11 Clifford Place, Greenpoint, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment building, 223 Franklin Street, Greenpoint, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - EXT Garrett's apartment, 15 Clifford Place, Greenpoint, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - INT Barge, Greenpoint Terminal, 73 West Street between Milton Street and Noble Street, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - INT/EXT Horvath's, 145 Kent Street, 2009 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Empty building, Greenpoint [73 West Street], circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Abandoned building, Greenpoint [60 West Street], circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Abandoned building, Greenpoint [West Street and Noble Street], circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - INT Apartment, 59 Green Street Apt. 3 at West Street, Greenpoint, circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Farmer Black's Garden, Eagle Street Rooftop Farms, 44 Eagle Street (between West Street and Franklin Street), Greenpoint, 2010 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - EXT Black Residential World, Greenpoint, circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    This folder includes photographs of McGuinness Boulevard, Eagle Street, West Street, India Street, Greenpoint Avenue, Manhattan Avenue, Meserole Street, Franklin Street, Dupont Street.
  - EXT Josh's Neighborhood, Greenpoint, circa 2010 (Box 32, Folder 16)